quebles.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy: Quebles.com

Privacy statement

**General**  
Quebles.com makes all reasonable and legally mandated efforts to protect your privacy. This Quebles.com Privacy Statement applies to the web sites where Quebles.com content is offered and relates to the collection and use of data through the Quebles.com services. The personal details of all users are collected, used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Statement.

**Collection of personal details**  
Quebles.com will ask you for personal details such as your e-mail address, name and your telephone number for example. Quebles.com may also collect demographic data such as your age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites. Some data is also collected about the hardware and software which you are using. This includes IP addresses, browsers, domain names, data on session duration and pages viewed. These data are used by Quebles.com to deliver the service and to maintain the quality of the service. These statistical data are also used to gain insight into the use of the services of Quebles.com. It is also recorded which Quebles.com content is viewed by our customers to determine which services are used the most. This information is used to support the development of specific content and advertising for customers who are interested in a particular subject. Quebles.com is not responsible for the privacy statements of others.

**Use of your personal details**  
Personal details are collected and used by Quebles.com and its associated service and product partners to operate Quebles.com, to deliver requested services, and to sell services/products. [Surveys may also be conducted to ask you for your opinion on current services or potential new services.] Quebles.com does not sell, rent or lease customer lists to third parties. [If you have given permission to do so, Quebles.com may from time to time contact you with specific offers which may be of interest to you. In such cases, your personal details (e-mail address, name and telephone number) will not be disclosed to third parties, but these offers will be handled by Quebles.com.] Quebles.com may disclose or open personal details when required by law or in case of a strong conviction that such action is necessary: (a) to comply with legal provisions or a summons addressed to Quebles.com; (b) to protect or defend the ownership rights of Quebles.com and its partners; or (c) in urgent situations, to ensure the personal safety of Quebles.com or others. Personal data collected from the web sites where Quebles.com content is offered, may be stored and processed in any country where Quebles.com or its affiliated companies, subsidiaries or agents have facilities in place.

**Security of your personal details**  
Quebles.com makes all reasonable efforts to protect your personal details. We use a variety of protection technologies and procedures to protect your personal details from unlawful access, use or disclosure. This includes storing your personal details on computer systems which can only be accessed by a limited number of persons, and which are housed in secure facilities.

**Inspecting and changing your personal data**  
Questions about our privacy policy, about inspecting or changes to (or deletion of) your personal data can be addressed to:

Our company address is: Koraalrood 100, 2718 SC , Zoetermeer, The Netherlands

Phone number: +31-(0)79-360 11 88  
Chamber of Commerce number: 27197080  
VAT number: 80.98.88.737-B01

When requesting an inspection or changes to your personal data, please send a copy of you passport for identification purposes, so that we are certain we will not provide any of your personal data to anyone else.

**Changes to this statement**  
Quebles.com updates this Privacy Statement from time to time in response to feedback from the company and from customers. Quebles.com recommends that you read this statement from time to time to keep up to date on the way in which Quebles.com secures your data.

This Privacy Statement was prepared on 17 November 2011.
